Seth Michael Atkinson

Home Address: 2733 Spencer Road, Mansfield, PA 16933 Telephone: (570) 404-3715

Email: atkinsonsm11@mounties.mansfield.edu Portfolio of work: https://ibreakthings.github.io/Portfolio2/

SUMMARY

I often find myself searching for new knowledge on subjects that I am interested in, taking my personal time to research and learn more about them. Also, I am strong problem solver, dedicating myself to an issue until I am able to achieve results. I find these skills often coming together to allow me to take on challenges beyond my skillset. I find that the situations in which I am presented with these challenges are the ones where I shine the brightest, and my drive for learning compels me to tackle issues intelligently.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Skill	Expertise Level	Skill	Expertise Level
Java	Intermediate	Microsoft Word	Expert
HTML 5	Advanced	Microsoft PowerPoint	Expert
CSS	Intermediate	Microsoft Excel	Expert
SQL / databases / MySQL	Advanced	Windows XP, 7, 10	Expert
JUnit Testing	Novice	NetBeans IDE	Intermediate
git / GitHub version control	Intermediate	Eclipse / STS IDE	Novice
Linux / Ubuntu 16.04	Intermediate	Vi / Vim	Intermediate
Linux Shell Scripts	Novice	Agile / Scrum	Advanced

PROJECTS

Game Review Website Spring 2015

Class project at Mansfield University

I was given a task to create a website for my Advance Web Design course, and I choose to make a site where I could review some of the latest games. We were given two weeks' time to create the website, which I finished using a mix of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap to create a mobile friendly and clean site. It was expanded to include 5 separate, recently released titles with a home page and easy navigation tools. I received an A- on the project overall, and the site received several votes for the, "Best Project," award.

Online Vendor Website

Class project at Mansfield University

During my Business Programming Concepts II class I was given the challenge of creating a website posing as an online vendor. My group came up with the idea of Keystar Computers, an online computer part vendor. The website contained a mix of HTML, CSS, and PHP. Then, using Google Cloud Management services created a LAMP server running on Ubuntu 16.04 and hosted our website on it. The project received an 'A' mark.

EDUCATION

Mansfield University of Pennsylvania

2013 - 2017

Bachelor of Science, Computer & Information Science (IS Track), Minor in Accounting, 3.5GPA.

Seth Michael Atkinson

Home Address: 2733 Spencer Road, Mansfield, PA 16933 Telephone: (570) 404-3715

Email: atkinsonsm11@mounties.mansfield.edu Portfolio of work: https://ibreakthings.github.io/Portfolio2/

AWARDS, ACTIVITIES, and HONORS

- Honor Roll 2011-2013
- Dean's List 2015
- Recognition Award Business 2014

EXPERIENCE

Business Support Services – Mansfield University

April 2014 – December 2015

Fixed Asset Manager's Assistant

While working with the Fixed Asset Manager, I was responsible for keeping track of millions of dollars' worth of equipment for Mansfield University. I used a database system paired with a physical labeling process to log acquisition, depreciation, and disposal of fixed assets.

Campus Technologies – Mansfield University

January 2016 – May 2017

Technician's Assistant

As a Technician's assistant, I would find myself often working with sudden and complex issues with hard and software throughout campus. Also, I was often called upon to preform regular maintenance and inspections of the university's Point-of-Sale services, including registers, scanners, and the Blackboard PoS system. Often I would be working directly with clients, who were faculty, staff, and students, in assisting them with problems or teaching them how to use various web-based services.

REFERENCES

Andy Havalchak – ahavalchak@gmail.com

Professor of Accounting and academic advisor.

Alex Miller – (607)731-7764 – amiller@mansfield.edu

Supervisor for Fixed Asset Management and Campus Technologies.

Tina Cassada – (607)481-5955 – tcassada@mansfield.edu

Supervisor and mentor for Campus Technologies.